叫我吉米就好
Oh, just "Jimmy" is fine.
吉米  很高兴见到你  快过来
Jimmy, pleasure. Come on down.
请坐
Have a seat.
亨利给你讲了我们在找什么样的人吧
Guessing Henry filled you in on what we're looking for.
他告诉我了
Oh, he did, indeed -- um
挨个办公室串的推销员
office-to-office salesman
能接受吃无数的闭门羹
willing to have multiple doors slammed in my face
只有一个任务
with one mission --
把他们的旧复印机升级  升级  升级成
upgrade, upgrade, upgrade their old copiers
你们的最新款
to your top-of-the-line new ones.
你觉得自己有这个本事吗
Well, you think you have the chops?
说得容易做起来可难多了
It's a lot harder than it sounds.
我很愿意尝试一下
Well, I'd sure love a crack at it.
人们都说  顽强  有说服力
I've been told stubbornness and persuasiveness
是我最突出的两个特点
are two of my top qualities.
我得说  吉米很了解复印机
I have to say, Jimmy does know his way around a copier.
是吗
No kidding.